[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a popular database name?", "correct_answer": "Oracle", "incorrect_answers": ["Mosque", "Shrine", "Church"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mink are mainly active at night and they do not hibernate. Which of these animals is a predator of the American Mink?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Wolf", "Owl", "Coyote"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What statement is true about elephants mammary glands?", "correct_answer": "They have one pair of mammary glands.", "incorrect_answers": ["They have two pairs of mammary glands.", "None of these", "They have only one mammary gland."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the traditional Chinese meal made from glutinous rice stuffed with different fillings and wrapped in bamboo or reed leaves, and cooked by steaming or boiling.", "correct_answer": "Zongzi", "incorrect_answers": ["Lamma cake", "Ma Ye", "Ai Wo Wo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do frogs have gills?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the great fortification built in 37-31 BC by Roman king Herod I on a high hill above the Dead Sea?", "correct_answer": "Masada", "incorrect_answers": ["Kadesh-Barnea", "Herods Citadel", "Vespasians Citadel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Andreas Gruenintzig was the doctor who first  performed this procedure.", "correct_answer": "Angioplasty", "incorrect_answers": ["Thyroidectomy", "Bone marrow transplant", "Lung transplant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Myanmar is a south-eastern Asian country. Under which name was it known before a military junta took over?", "correct_answer": "Burma", "incorrect_answers": ["Siam", "Bhutan", "Noth Vietnam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The most garbage collecting volunteers gathered in this US state.", "correct_answer": "California", "incorrect_answers": ["Ohio", "Texas", "New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what U.S. state was actor Richard Gere born?", "correct_answer": "Pennsylvania", "incorrect_answers": ["Maryland", "Delaware", "West Virginia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was Butterfly McQueen born?", "correct_answer": "1/ 7/ 1911", "incorrect_answers": ["1/7/1921", "1/7/1926", "1/7/1930"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Felix Silla has been in many movies and TV shows, however, he played his most favourite role in this TV comedy show from 1964-1966.", "correct_answer": "The Addams Family", "incorrect_answers": ["My Favorite Martian", "My Mother the Car", "The Munsters"]}]